[
{
    "id": 1,
    "question": "How many stars?",
    "question_2": "*******",
    "answer": [7,2,8,6],
    "correct": "7",
    "type": "app",
    "level": 1
},
{
    "id": 2,
    "question": "How many stars?",
    "question_2": "********** ********** **********",
    "answer": [30,80,10,20],
    "correct": "30",
    "type": "app",
    "level": 1
},
{
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Fill the gaps:",
    "question_2": "10, 20, ___,40, 50",
    "answer": [60,30,70,80],
    "correct": "30",
    "type": "app",
    "level": 1
},
{
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Fill the gaps:",
    "question_2": "101, 102, ___,104, 105",
    "answer": [106,103,109,100],
    "correct": "103",
    "type": "app",
    "level": 1
},
{
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What’s the number?",
    "question_2": "100 + 50 + 5 = ___",
    "answer": [160, 150, 155,165],
    "correct": "155",
    "type": "video",
    "level": 1
},
{
    "id": 6,
    "question": "How many stars?",
    "question_2": "********** ********** ********** **********",
    "answer": [20,80,40,30],
    "correct": "40",
    "type": "app",
    "level": 2
},
{
    "id": 7,
    "question": "How many stars?",
    "question_2": "********** ********** ********** ********** ********** ********** **********",
    "answer": [10,70,50,60],
    "correct": "70",
    "type": "app",
    "level": 2
},
{
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Fill the gaps:",
    "question_2": "5, 10, ___,20, 25",
    "answer": [15,11,20,35],
    "correct": "15",
    "type": "app",
    "level": 2
},
{
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Fill the gaps:",
    "question_2": "997, 998, 999, ___",
    "answer": [1000,106,900,996],
    "correct": "1000",
    "type": "app",
    "level": 2
},
{
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What’s the number?",
    "question_2": "200 + 60 + 8 = ___",
    "answer": [268, 168, 257,278],
    "correct": "268",
    "type": "video",
    "level": 2
}
]
